Let us know
how you can change and update policy details in ICICI LBR
with Mr. Policy.  First you have to install
IL Take Care app from Google Play Store or Apple App Store.
After installation, enter the registered mobile
number.  After entering the number,
complete the verification with OTP.
After verification is done, you will now see the
Policies option on the home screen of the app.
Click on it.  As soon as you click, you will be
shown the option of update policy.
Click on it [Music] and
click on New Request.  Now here you will be
shown the option of customer details and nominee details.
And you can check the status of previous [Music] requests below.
You can change your address, mobile
number and email ID by clicking on Customer [nasal sound] details.  If
you need to change any other [Music] details
like DOB and name you have to mail or
call the company.  Normally
you can change name, DOB and relationship by clicking on details.
After making the changes, recheck the details and
after checking and confirming the terms and conditions,
click on Update.  And within seven working days
you will receive the updated policy on your registered mail
ID.  If you have any
question or query then you
can comment.  Follow Mr. Policy
for more informative videos.